Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 1: Boxes 1-22 1870-2017
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Continental Corp., Publication (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Bulletin: Growing Local Business, Publication (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: The Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: 1989 Annual Report, Publication (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Currents, Publication (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Vol. 3 No. 6 June. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Currents, Publication (Box 11, Folder 11)
    July Vol. 3 No. 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Currents, Publication (Box 11, Folder 11)
    May Vol. 3 No. 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Continental Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Continental Grain Co., Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: A World of Growth in Agribusiness, Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: 1981 Positional Descriptions, Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Continental Group, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Continental Group, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Carrying A Better Life Around The World, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: On The Job How Continental Works, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Continental Insurance Company, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Courier, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Vol. 8 No. 2 Feb. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Courier, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Vol. 8 No. 3 March. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Continental Insurance Bulleting, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: The Courier, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Vol. 8 No. 1 Jan. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Item 11: Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Item 12: Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Item 13: Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Item 14: Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Item 15: Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Item 16: The Courier, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Vol. 7 No. 1 Jan. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Courier, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Vol. 8 No. 5 May. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Continental People, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
    vol. 3 No. 9 Sept. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Courier, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Vol. 7 No. 3 March. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Courier, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Vol. 7 No. 6 June. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Courier, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Vol. 7 No. 9 Sept. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: The Courier, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
    vol. 7 No. 4 April. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Continental People, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
    vol. 3 No. 11 Nov. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
    winter. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Continental People, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Vol. 3 No. 7 July. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: The Courier, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Vol. 6 No. 5oct. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Continental People, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Vol. 3 No. 5 May. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: The Courier, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Vol. 6 No. 1 Feb. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Continental People, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Vol. 3 No. 3 March. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: The Courier, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Vol. 6 No. 6 Dec. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: RCA Organization Questionairre, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Continental Insurance Co., Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Courier, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
    Vol. 7 No. 2 Feb. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: Currents, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
    Vol. 2 No. 6 Aug/Sept. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Continental Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 9: continental Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: Currents Vol. 3 No. 2 Feb, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 11: Continental Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 12: Currents, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
    Vol. 3 No. 9 Oct. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Currents, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
    Vol. 3 No. 8 Aug/Sept. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Continental Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 15: Continental Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 16: Currents, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
    Vol. 4 No. 2 Feb. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Continental Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 18: Currents, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
    Vol. 4 No. 1 Jan. Item is in English.
- Continental Insurance Co., Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Continental Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Currents, Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
    Vol. 4 No. 4 Aug. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Currents, Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Your Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: Your Guide To Office Safety, Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: Non-exempt Performance Appraisal, Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: Continental Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: Continental Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Item 9: Continental Benefits: Your Benefits in 1991, Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Cooper & Secret Association, Publication (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Contact, Publication (Box 11, Folder 17)
    Vol. 10 No. 4 July/Aug. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Chronology Key Elements in Control Data's History, Publication (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Control Data Corporation, Publication (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Corporate Profile, Publication (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Catastrophic Medicare Polling Update, Publication (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Coors, Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Working for Coors With A Life Detector Strapped To Your Body, Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
    By David Sickler. Item is in English.
- Copper Development Association, Publication (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Publications, Publication (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Cornell University NYSSILR, Publication (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: 1988-1992 Agreement Between Cornell University and Cornell Service and Maintenance Unit, Publication (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Management Industrial Relations Workshop Series, Publication (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Preparation for Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 11, Folder 20)
    By Morgan L. Pape. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Costing Out The Collective Bargaining Agreement Exercises & Reading, Publication (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Item 5: Preparation for Collective Bargaining A Guide For Union Negotiators, Publication (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Eli Lilly and Company, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Key Issues Legislative, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Key Issues Legislative, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: EIA 1981 Trade Directory and Membership Lsit, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Multi-year Contracting and Multi-year Funding presented by the Electronic Industries Asociation, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Publications Index, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Publications Index, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Electronic Market Data Book, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Executive Report, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Feb-Mar. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: News release, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Electronic Industries Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Statement of Peter F. McClosky, President Electronic Industries Association before the Subcommittee on Transportation, Aviation & communication of the U.S. House of representatives Committee on Science & Technology in the matter of The Federal Aviation Ad, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Statement of the telephone Equipment section, of the communications division, EIA In the matter of HR 5022, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: EIA Info, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Consumer electronics Group Quarterly Review, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: 1992 HRC Mail List and committee Sign up, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Human resources council members, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Benchmarking News, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Memorandum, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Feb 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Speakers' Biographies, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Memorandum, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Nov 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: A history of the Human Resources Council, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Cornell Cooperative Extension for the Coalition. Coalition for the Unemployed, Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A Guide for the Unemployed, Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Cornell. ILR. Extension Division, Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Producing Effective Video in the Field with Little Money (And Questionable Talent), Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Cornell. ILR. Institute for Workplace Studies, Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Workplace Colloqium Series, Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Cornell/PERC Institute on Conflict Resolution - The Appropriate Resolution of Corporate Disputes: A Report on the Growing Use of ADR by U.S. Corporations, 1998; Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Appropriate Resolution of Corporate Disputes: A Report on the Growing Use of ADR by U.S. Corporations, Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
    By David B. Lipsky and Ronald L. Seeber. Item is in English.
- Corning Glass Workers, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: National Constitution American Flint Glass Workers Union AFL CIO, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: A Tool for Quality: The Performance Development and Review, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Performance Management System Information, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: More Facts About Protection, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Corning Welcome!, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Corning Benefits, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Benefit Summary, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Application for Salaried Employment, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Applicant Interview Questionnaire, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: The Corporation strategies, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Information for New Corning Glass Works Employees, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Instructions for Moving Household Effects to New Location for New Corning Glass Works Employees, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Applicant Expense Report, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Corning Strategies for the 80s, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Pre-retirement Planning Program At Corning Glass Works, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: Performance Development and Review Interview Guide (PD&R) Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: Performance Development & Review Questionaire Administrative & Technical Personnel, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 18: Performance Development & Review Interview Questionnaire, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 19: The Gaffer, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 20: Channel Two, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 21: Corning Benefits Overview, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 22: Business Reply Mail Channel Two Coordinator, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 23: Corning: A vision, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 24: Corning Overview Brochure, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 25: Corning Benefits Protection, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Corporation for Enterprise Development, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Playing By New Rules: Nine Economic Development Realities for the 90's, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: The 1992 Development Report Card for the States: Executive Summary, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: The 1992 Development Report Card for the States: Executive Summary, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Bidding For Business: Are Cities and States Selling Themselves Short?, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: The 1994 Development Report Card For The States: Executive Summary, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Bidding For Business: Are Cities and States Selling Themselves Short?, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Council for American Fashion, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Ergonomics Project, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Ergonomics, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Ergonomics Project, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Fashion Forward, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Vol. 1 No. 2 Sept. Item is in English.
- Council of Communication Management, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: CCM/Mercer Communication Issues Phone Survey, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Council on Union-Free Environment, Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Council On Union-Free Environment An Organization for Positive and Progressive Employee Relations, Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Council On Union-Free Environment An Organization for Positive and Progressive Employee Relations: New Employee Orientation - The Mt. holly Experience, Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Council On Union-Free Environment An Organization for Positive and Progressive Employee Relations Private Sector Unions in the Political Arena, Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Council On Union-Free Environment An Organization for Positive and Progressive Employee Relations, Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Through the Looking Glass A Company's Self-Analysis Following a Union Organizational Campaign. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Council On Union-Free Environment An Organization for Positive and Progressive Employee Relations, Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
    A Tomorrow You Can Count On. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: A Quality and Performance Strategy for Supervisory Training, Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Council On Union-Free Environment An Organization for Positive and Progressive Employee Relations, Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
    A Collection of Union-Free Position Statements. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Council On Union-Free Environment An Organization for Positive and Progressive Employee Relations, Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Making the Performance Appraisal Work. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Council On Union-Free Environment An Organization for Positive and Progressive Employee Relations, Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
    People, Their Values and How To Manage Them. Item is in English.
- Council on Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: For the Electrical Contracting Industry, Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Council on Industrial relations for the Electrical Contracting Industry, Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: A Guide For Submission of a Case to the Council on Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: The Council on Industrial Relations for the Electrical Contracting Industry, Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Council on Industrial Relations for the Electrical Contracting Industry, Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Crafted With Pride in U.S.A. Council, Publication (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Crafted With Pride U.S.A. Council, Publication (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Crouse-Hinds-Handbook, Manuals, etc., Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Cooper Industries Summary of Benefits, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Who Are Our Customers?, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: History of Crouse-Hinds, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Full Service Capabilities, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Cooper Industries, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Crouse-Hinds News, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
    Special Issue Dec. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Crouse-Hinds News, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
    Specjaine Grudzien. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Crouse-Hinds News, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
    Edicion Especial Diciembre. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 9: Crouse-Hinds News, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
    Item is in Spanish.
- Crown Zellerbach Corporation, Publication (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Resource, Publication (Box 12, Folder 13)
    Summer. Item is in Spanish.
- Hodgson Andrews, Publication (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining Agreements Microfilms B-003208-84, Publication (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Dahlstrom & Company, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Surviving a Layoff, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Dana Corporation, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: People Finding A Better Way, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: The Philosophy & Policies of DANA, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: The Dana Style, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Dana Info, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: Product and Service Guide, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: The Philosophy & Policies of Dana, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: The Direction of Dana, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: The Dana Style, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Item 9: Dana Communicator's Newsletter, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
    Aug 18. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 10: Dana Communicator's Newsletter, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
    Sept 22. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 11: Dana communicator's Newsletter, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
    Oct 22. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 12: Dana Communicator's Newsletter, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
    Nov 20. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 13: Dana Communicator's Newsletter, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
    Dec 17. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 14: 2000, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Item 15: The dana Style, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Item 16: The Direction of Dana, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Item 17: The Philosophy & Policies of Dana, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Item 18: Products, Systems and Services, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Item 19: Dana 2000, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Item 20: The Philosophy & Policies of Dana, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Item 21: The Dana Style, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Item 22: Dana Info, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Item 23: Dana Info, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Deere & Company, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Modern Materials Handling, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: The Story of John Deere, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Managing Energy For A Brighter Tomorrow, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Historical Highlights John Deere Contributions to Farm Mechanization, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: A Concern for the Total Environment, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: John Deere Careers and You, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: Deere & Company Administrative Center, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 8: Deere & Company Administrative Center, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 9: Employee Benefit Program, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 10: General Information, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 11: Management Principles, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 12: Management Principles, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 13: To John Deere Employees, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 14: Employee Benefit Program, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 15: The Story of John Deere, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 16: Historical highlights John Deere contributions to farm mechanization, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 17: JD Journal, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 18: John Deere Careers and You, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 19: Management Principles, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 20: John Deere Corporate Support Program, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 21: General Information, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 22: Code of Business Principles, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 23: Deere Today: New Challenges, New Spirit, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 24: Management Principles, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 25: General Information, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 26: Historical Highlights, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 27: John Deere, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 28: John Deere, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 29: General Information, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 30: Employee Benefit Program, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 31: Deere Power Systems, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Delta Airlines, Publication (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: This Is Delta, Publication (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Delta Digest, Publication (Box 12, Folder 18)
    Jan. Item is in Spanish.
- Detroit Diesel Allison, Publication (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Inside Detroit Diesel Allison: Diesel Operations, Publication (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Detroit Edison Company, Publication (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Job opportunities bulletin, Publication (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Letter to Ms. Ellen Sharaga, Publication (Box 12, Folder 20)
    aug 3. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 3: Employe Services Department, Publication (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Development Dimensions, Inc., Publication (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Assessment Technology: Revealing the Patterns of Individual Performance, Publication (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Applying A Systems Approach to Personnel Activities, Publication (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Targeted Selection a System for Identifying the Highest Quality Job Candidates, Publication (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Walt Disney Company, Publication (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: gift giving notes, Publication (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Doubleday, Publication (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Doubleday Info, Publication (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Dow Chemical Company, Publication (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Dow Benefit Plans and Programs, Publication (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: Quality of Life at Dow, Publication (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: Up With Life Is For Everyone, Publication (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: Quality Performance Means More At Dow, Publication (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Item 5: 1986 Annual Report, Publication (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Item 6: Recruiting & College Relations Department, Publication (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Item 7: Reaffirmation of Equal Employment Opportunity and Employment of Handicapped And Vietnam Veterans, Publication (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Item 8: You Can Do Great Things At Dow, Publication (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Item 9: 1982 Information Handbook, Publication (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Item 10: Information Handbook 1980, Publication (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Item 11: Dow and the Work Environment, Publication (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Item 12: Dow Info, Publication (Box 12, Folder 24)